>> Brian Holt: 现在在您的目录中，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Now inside
of your directory,
我们要去做个新文件夹
inside of source we're
gonna make a new folder.
这只会被称为 actionCreator。
And that one's gonna be
called actionCreators.
这不一定是要求，但我觉得这是有用的，
This isn't necessarily a requirement,
but I find this to be helpful and
我想说很多人都这么做
I would say many people do it.
有时人会直接创建操作，但是
Sometimes people will just
directly create the actions, but
我们会创造行动的创造者
we're gonna make action creators.
所以我们要做这个，这个叫做 ChangeLocation.js。
So we're going to make this one, this
one's gonna be called ChangeLocation.js.
这将会导出一个函数
And this is just going
to export a function
称为导出缺省函数。
called export default function.
>> Brian Holt: changeLocation，在一个位置中，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: changeLocation,
that takes in a location,
它返回类型为 CHANGE_LOCATION的对象，
and it returns an object
of type: CHANGE_LOCATION,
有效载荷将被定位
and payload is going to be location.
>> Brian Holt: 这是一个动作的样子，对吧 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: This is what
an action looks like, right?
这就是一个行动的创造者，对吧 ?
So this is an action creator, right?
它是一个功能，你给它一个位置它让你有一个行动。
It's a function that you give it
a location it gives you back an action.
>> Brian Holt: 再次，人们有时会直接发送对象，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And again, people will just
sometimes directly dispatch objects that
就像这样
look like this.
我也没问题的
I'm fine with that as well.
但我要教你这样更有条理的方法
But I'm just gonna teach you kind of
the more structured way to do it, and
那我就把它留给你做你想做的
then I'll leave it up to
you how you wanna do it,
>> Brian Holt: 好吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay?
> > Brian Holt: 我们会在这里再做一个，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: We're gonna
make one more here, and
这将叫做 changetheme.js。
this is going to be called changetheme.js.
看起来相对相同， changeTheme(主题)，
Looks relatively the same,
changeTheme(theme),
主题和 CHANGE_THEME， >> Brian Holt: 好吗 ?
theme and CHANGE_THEME,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay?